Staring [cheering voice]
Starring and Welcome Shubham Pujari.
Hello Hello
How are you guys?
This is great, I like it very much Mumbai
About this. How excited are you?
I come back happy from home.
So many people are seeing comedy for the first time.
Among the people. Someone who is the first time
Watching a comedy. You guys, one or two people.
Okay, are you guys 18 plus?
[Laughter]
What is your age?
I am definitely not lying. The police come
Is it here?
[Cheers]
Don't worry. Come after the show
[laughter] It's the police.
Ok. Ok. Welcome to the show. Welcome to
The show. and any parents
come with [throat clearing sound] and so on
Has gone. By mistake, tell me now. We tell
Are there any two who are parents? Everybody's friends
Only they are. What?
Is there that much juice?
No, no, there's nothing like that, but you came.
With anyone? [Laughter]
Who have you come with?
Two Friends
Two friends. Ok, good. and someone else
You can also date one of these
We Menting Butt
Well why [laughs].
Oh that is interesting.
Why Didn't You Die?
Different things you were clear?
Were we clear?
It's two years.
Let me tell you you're clear.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
He still wants the same things. [Laughter]
This is a recording show. We are from YouTube
Recording for. Mumbai gives me every
The bar looks great. I first
I had also uploaded the video from here. and like
Neither this is a small audience from anywhere. You
There is at least some fire inside you.
Like in the middle of the show, you'll feel like
That
[Laughter]
That mine is better. Yes
Which is the truth. Yes, that is absolutely true
The thing is. The audience has become very funny. tomorrow I
Came live with a friend. Usap
People are commenting. two brothers both
Sweet.
How will I win the audience? So you also have a lot
There will be a fire in the middle of the show, not like that, friend.
I also want to say something but you are here today.
Avoid it or we'll go out after the show.
We will meet there and talk. Ok?
[Laughter]
Because then you will say something.
Then I'll look like a fool, so I'll [laughs].
I don't want this to be on camera for everyone.
Front. Ok? Let me tell you a little about myself
I will tell you guys. I me very
I am ashamed to say that I
I am a resident of Mirzapur. [Laughter]
And I've been living here for quite some time now.
In Delhi. I've been there seven or eight years.
While living. I keep coming to Mumbai for stand up
For. I keep going to Bangalore. big
I keep roaming around the city. But now my strength
I am suffocating. [sound of clearing throat] One
There is a strange pressure on me. a bit strange
There is pressure. The pressure to be open-minded.
Is it up to you guys too? I am watching
I am a small minded person, I don't want to keep anyone here.
Are giving. In which I am comfortable.
Which is my comfort zone. You will instantly get points
Will throw you out. Yes. black filth on the mouth
Will give you someone's thinking, stay away from small things.
This is such bad behavior. Yes. These
What shallow behavior. Discrimination
It is on the basis of thoughts.
That someone's thinking is small. On that basis you
You are discriminating him. Our
Side discrimination is easy. We are going
Let's ask.
Disposes instantly, chill with it
To do it or not to do it.
Here I see people in the big city
You are making the vibe match, right? that my vibe
I will sit with him when the match happens. then I
I will sit with it. How to match the vibe
Brother, am I with anyone? I don't even know
What's my vibe? [Laughter]
I look like a secret patient.
I don't understand whose vibe I'm matching with.
I am coming. And you know small thinking, right?
To the people? Yes. which would have been your first thought
looking at anything [laughs]
that good
Three months with him, four months with her
Then back with him for three months, yes,
Your first thought about anything is
seeing. But look at how much brain
God made it complicated. How much
Beautifully made. When you think and when
You say thousands of people in between.
Processes happen in your brain
Inside. First, thought arises in the brain.
Then in the language area of ​​the brain, the word
Are selected. The brain then sends signals
How will the tongue move? which moves how
will be? How will the words be formed? Sentence
How the entire speech is planned. And
When you're here thinking, well, three
A month with him, four months with her. These
There are so many processes. When travel
He does it and when he leaves from here, he does something like this
It is heard that everyone has their own life.
[Appreciation]
Who are we to judge anyone?
Small thinking [laughs]
And your thinking is small. You don't know
Is. People tell this openly and go away.
As if I had just come to Delhi. My
The college was in Delhi and I was a student of the college.
I met a girl in my initial days and
We became friends. It's telling everything
About your life till 12th
He had a very good relationship. Then
She broke up with him before he came to college.
Did it.
I said when we had a good relationship
Why did you break up? She is saying friend
The boy was a little too good.
I said, meaning he has no one of his own
There were no opinions. I say left
So he would have gone left. If I say right
It would have been right. like dough
Was.
You should be molded the way I mold you.
used to go. I said you are the best boy.
So there is the green flag. Say no to green flags
It is a dark green flag. [Laughter]
Bangladesh
And we girls need the green flag too.
Does not happen. What are you saying? say we
People need a little red flag. yes this
There may be some struggle in the relationship, yes
I want attention but I am not getting it.
[laughter] So they're stealing attention. Yes. Little
Dopamine should be released. Yes. 24 such
I don't need an available rickshaw boy
Kind.
Yes, all the boys you have
I should basically tell the girls that I am a spoiled person.
I want a boy. which on daily basis
Improve little by little.
So that there is a sense of achievement every day. Yes.
[Laughter]
What did I do today? If I [ __ ] the nun
Made a little improvement.
You will find a ready-made boy and kick him.
She drives me away. People, yes, a spoiled brat
Pakadeng will improve it gradually. Daily
Will create small battles. by himself
If you win, you will become happy yourself. [Laughter]
Girls have a dating pattern
Brother. And when that boy is properly dressed like this
Goes over the year. to leave them to someone else
He leaves with . [Laughter]
This is a dating pattern for girls and
I am speaking in defense of that boy.
I am because I can relate a lot.
I am from that boy. I said, friend, you
How did you let him go? yes so good
The boy was such a perfect boy. Then my
A voice comes from inside saying, you idiot. [laughter] This
This is not the time to defend that boy.
This is the time to lend a shoulder, right? [Laughter]
And my shoulder was a virgin shoulder at that time.
No girl had ever cried with her head on it.
Yes. It was only useful for hanging the bag.
Now suddenly a beautiful out of the box girl is coming to this
She wants to cry by placing her head on it. what evil
Is? [Laughter]
And when I spoke in his support,
I became doubtful about the boy. girls
After the break, there is a lot of doubtful going around.
Asks for validation from here and there. doubtful
That's done. Saying Did I Make a Mistake?
My friends also keep saying that you
I made a mistake by leaving him. did I make a
Mistake? I said the opportunity is good. [Laughter]
You are saying the same thing. Did
Did I make a mistake? I said a girl like
You can never make a mistake?
I said, Sir, I came here immediately. Yes.
Gradually our friendship progressed. Conversation
Moved ahead. And slowly that friendship grew
She went and converted into such a relationship. These
The entire story is about that relationship.
It is around. The first phase of a relationship
Yes, that is fictional fuzz. [laughter] In that
You would be roaming around happily like idiots.
Your whole life is ruined. Yes.
But you are having fun. Yes. you all day long
You are roaming around happily. hair looking in the mirror
You are making it. Yes. [laughter] College 10:00 AM
You are sitting ready at 6:00. Attendance
75 is my 750.
You are roaming around happily like a mad person. Yes.
[laughter] Yes. Very very fictional face
It happens brother. A girl comes into your life
Is. 100 bad things start looking good.
Sitting covered with polythene but enjoying it
Is. [Laughter]
It feels like I'm sitting in a golden palace.
You are there.
A girl is talking to you on the phone all day long.
Is that Did You Reach Home Safely? yours
Why is fiber intake so low? [Laughter]
Why don't you eat fruits? hey i
I don't eat fruits because fruits are my lunch.
It is more expensive than.
In my family, we eat fruits only when we are home.
There is a story on it. [Laughter]
I come from such a family, brother, that's why fruits
I don't eat. And a very out of place girl
Was. Like we used to talk on the phone every day.
I called one day at night. I
I saw songs playing behind, there was noise.
There is alcohol and hustle and bustle. I asked what
Happened? Have you gone out somewhere? Don't say it at home
Yes I am. Actually it was grandfather's birthday.
So we gave Grandpa a surprise birthday.
The party has been given. Do you understand? What
Did she come from a family? [Laughter]
It was a grandfather's birthday, so he told his grandfather
Has given a surprise to. I am my grandfather
Should I surprise him? Grandfather will die.
[Laughter]
Now there is nothing left inside grandfather. Yes.
We keep protecting them. Yes.
Just the day before yesterday I washed the dishes in the kitchen. grandfather Sir
I peed in my pants. [Laughter]
You think my grandfather's body
Will she be able to handle the surprise? His body will be able to withstand
Surprise yes? I will finish you off, grandfather.
[Laughter]
I know that grandfather has passed away completely. Done
Happy birthday brother. [Laughter]
[sound of clearing throat]
My thinking is small. [Laughter]
This girl told me.
Yes, I had no idea at all brother.
We were in college. We have a common
I was a friend in college. His name was Ishaan.
We had a common friend. common friend
What was it? He was his friend. [Laughter]
I had to consider it common.
Let me tell you the truth. My pubic hair was burning
After seeing him. [Laughter]
I was in the process of wrapping up the opportunity
meet. So we used to hang out together in college.
In. We used to chill together. I mean, these people
Used to chill. I used to hang out with them.
[Laughter]
So I noticed when I came to New Delhi
I was very shy. I noticed that
When college is over, I
I am walking away every day holding hands with my girlfriend.
Am.
Every day [sound of clearing throat] I hug
I am having it with him.
[Applause] So for the first few days I
Ignored it. Yes. What did you ignore? I
I cried alone.
[Laughter]
I was not able to ignore it. This much
I am not strong. Then magazine point
I gathered courage and said, friend, this is it
Not right. So the girl got angry at me.
that one second one second one second you open
Are you not minded?
And I was completely broken from inside brother because
Where I come from, it's the most open
I am minded.
[Appreciation]
It is easy to be open minded in a small town.
I am very easy to be open minded. you in the evening
Wear half pants and go out for a walk. open
Minded.
[Laughter]
Here in the big city, people have made it tough.
Is. And God sent that girl.
It was to make me open minded. Our
There was always a fight over this. you so much
How can you be narrow minded? How there
Can you be so narrow-minded? one day at least
She started fighting with me that yesterday you filled the metro.
I called a boy gay.
I said because in the crowded metro
The boy buried my game.
[Appreciation]
And he didn't even press it with love. yes like
My friends press me. [Laughter]
He has pounced. of escaping robbery
tried.
[laughter] I squeezed so hard it hurt my stomach.
It felt like mine.
A current ran through my body. saying here
Then you would have abused him. you him
Would have slapped me. But you chose to call him
Again. Because you think being gay is a
It is an abuse. There is a curse. You know this
People go through so much trauma.
No one wants to be friends with them. These
People don't make you feel inclusive. with these
He doesn't get up or sit down. feeling of hatred towards them
Let's see from. I said this is all mine
It happens together too.
Have I also gone? [laughter] Do you
Does all this seem like a joke? you thought you were joking
You will never understand their mental trauma.
Because you never wanted to be friends with them.
Didn't even try. Is there any home friend?
yours? He asked with such authority that
I counted all my friends one by one.
I said what are you talking about? Ravi [laughs]
is gay
Aadarsh ​​C is Pratik and Vishwas is a lesbian
Is
[Appreciation]
Gagan Pandey is a eunuch, are you crazy?
yes what
[laughter] Are you out of your mind?
It's a joke here, these people are Galesbians.
No, you call them sweet and sweet.
[Laughter]
So that you can make fun of them. I said
What are you talking about? My whole circle
Hee is so woke. I know how woke it is
Your circle? I remember people went to dinner.
Call the waiter with your circle
Your people are there. [Laughter]
After eating, I asked what was for dessert.
Eat? I took out tuberose from your pocket
with.
I said, so what is the problem Rajnigandha?
[Laughter]
Its taste is tuberose.
So your friends also smoke cigarettes.
Are. [sound of clearing throat]
She hits neat. I say you have to understand this
donkeys
[sound of clearing throat][laughter] that cigarette
Drinking is a status symbol. while eating gutkha
Is there an address proof?
It tells you where you come from?
Say we are sitting in such a nice restaurant.
Your friends' phone rang. Vibe
Ruined the entire restaurant. [Laughter]
My friends use customized ringtones.
Are.
What is the problem with this ringtone?
Didn't you hear that tiding ting ringtone?
Tuding hello [laughs]
tudding ting tudding hello
Ting Ting Ting Adarsh ​​ji please pick up your phone
Ideal
[Appreciation]
Best ringtone bro. I am very useless
Why did you feel it? I said very emotional.
Always feeling narrow minded in small spaces
How can you say what happened, I said when
You have so many problems, my narrow one.
being minded because of my small space
So why did you come into a relationship with me?
Let me tell you why did you start all this?
Why should you even start because you
Shubham started pleading [laughs]
I rejected you before, yes.
Then you put a blade on your wrist and send me a photo.
started
You are sending your selfie with a harp
Then I did not agree that the boy is okay, let's go
I will give it a chance and see. small
I can't tolerate your reaction. talk
You start crying over every little thing. look again
Started crying. You started crying again. I am emotional
Was. As soon as you started scolding me.
I had an emotional breakdown. I
He started crying softly. it calmed me down
That sit and don't create a scene. Everybody see
Don't create a scene. [laughter] As many
also people among you in relationship
I give people an advice. a trick
Let me tell you basically. ever been in a relationship
Your fight starts getting so out of hand that
You don't understand this fight.
How to stop it? How to pacify this anger
Let's do? Start shouting loudly that scene
Don't create, don't create a scene, don't create a scene
Create it. Yes. So your partner feels
Hey sisterfucker, a scene is being created.
What? [Laughter]
Then the fights suddenly get diverted.
As soon as it started screaming, I
I became conscious. It made me sit on my
I did it on my back like dogs do.
Are. I opened this purse and found a juice bottle in it.
Took out the bottle. He said, take this and drink it. You will feel
Better.
And I opened the bottle. I was just about to drink.
Then I thought, friend, the girl who is so close to me
She hates me, I'm always narrow-minded
Small place understands all this on her juice.
should not be trusted
It could contain anything, yes.
I said [sound of clearing throat] before
you drink
She became happy and said, look at these small things.
yours looks good
[Appreciation]
Shivilary yes now how do I tell my
I am saving your life brother, consider this as a shivalry.
She kept drinking this juice and remained alive, then I
I also drank juice and sugar drinks your anger
I calm down and I start feeling better
Then she started explaining to me, look this is a
Relationships: This is how we grow as a
Person na things you don't understand
I will explain that to you and the things that I
I don't understand that eventually
I will figure it out
This is how we grow as a person, na maine
said yes this is how we grow as a person
I started to feel better, I realized
That she does all this for my good. Then
It is evening time and we are sitting like this.
A cool breeze is blowing. the sun is setting
Is. Spending quality time is very important
I am feeling good. That's when I saw
An aunty is leaving. She was from his neighbourhood.
I said, hey, your neighbor aunty
Nor those who are having an affair with someone.
I said it again, friend. Yes. dizzy
It is not working. She is just exploring
Herself.
I said but she is also married.
This is not called cheating. say cheating then
When the husband speaks like a husband
Behave. Her husband is at home half the time.
It doesn't come to me. I said because he
He goes to work. [Laughter]
Even when he stays for half the time, their
The fight continues. He comes home drunk
He makes a spectacle. You know one
How many problems are there in relationships?
Yes. Not excited about their anniversary
Would. Not excited about his birthday
Would. I don't plan trips for them.
Doesn't plan travel. And she has all the
Right to Find That Love in Someone Else. And
Why are you judging them so much? You
Are you not open minded? Look so far
I thought I was very open-minded.
Am. The world just doesn't understand me.
[laughter] Maybe my way of being open-minded.
It is different. After this conversation, I was completely
I came down on the ground and thought, sisterfucker, how low I am.
I am a man. that on a woman like a goddess
[Laughter]
I doubted it. I feel very useless
It is installed. I started feeling very bad.
I started feeling very guilty, but very
It was an important conversation of my life.
Because after this I came to know that open
How do you become minded? Tremble
[sound of clearing throat] No. you guys
I will also tell you that it is very easy. Look at whatever
Things seem offensive to you. Out of league
It seems that this is outside my culture.
It is a thing of. This is my belief system.
Is against. You adopt him. Yes.
That maybe you are the idiot. So now I open
I am becoming minded. Yes. just me
I don't know where to stop.
I have become very open minded. Infact
I also have questions for you guys.
I have brought it prepared. Someone among you
Someone who came from a small town and was quite
Living in a city bigger than Time. Yes
Brother, where are you from?
Yumpy? Ok. The way you yumpi
I have said it.
[Appreciation]
[Laughter]
You are from a small town. Ok. None of this
There is no doubt at all. [Laughter]
Ok. Someone who wants to beat up Yumpy
Is? Yes, you tell me brother.
Jhunjhunu [laughs]
Jhunjhunu.
Jhunjhunu
You have named it yourself, friend.
Do you call it lovingly or Jhunjhunu? Where
Do you live here? I live in Jhunjhunu. Ok. from you
Let me ask you a question. He has two options. You
Tell me what you think is right. Correct? One
She is a girl. Ok? There is a girl and she is together
She is dating two boys. Because
There are certain qualities you like in a guy.
She is having it. Some qualities in others
You are looking good. So right now he's confused
That's why she is dating both of them simultaneously.
Is. So tell me if that girl is right.
Or [sound of clearing throat] just your thoughts.
Is it small?
[Appreciation]
What happened, why did you start peeing?
It is a small thought. [laughter] Very, very correct answer.
He gave it brother. Ok. [Appreciation]
How many years have you been living here?
How many years have you been living in Mumbai?
happened?
One month.
Ok. Ok. You will stay for another year and a half.
Your diploma will be completed. Open-minded
In. Yes. Then you can tell the girl the right thing.
You will be hurt.
So now I'm much more open-minded.
Am. Now I am not on the receiving end.
The receiving end is the pay world. [Laughter]
Like I have a friend named Deepanshu. His
It was a birthday. It was during college time. His
It was a birthday. On his birthday he
Called friends. school friends, college friends
Friends, neighborhood friends. So Deepanshu's
I have friends from all walks of life. That range is mine
It starts from and goes up like this
From South Delhi to South Bombay girls
It reaches there. So it was his birthday. He
Directly called everyone for clubbing. Now I
He did not drink or anything else. Me too
He went away like a fool. Now I am someone
I go to the party. my uncle's
The behavior remains. I will go thought
It is Deepanshu's birthday. bless him
Give.
I will taste two or four items. Yes. and 9:30 p.m.
I will do it like this and leave. I have come. people
He made me sit. I said I
I don't drink. They lamed
And so on were caught. I sat down with a lemonade
Went. Now those people, his friends, they are enjoying a lot.
Are doing. Doing dance once. Look now
I am very open minded. Any
There is no scope for that. Too much open
I am minded. But I am still someone
I see the girl with golden hair.
[Laughter]
Then my hands and legs start trembling.
I am not made of the clay that a
Talking confidently to a Golden Ba girl
I can get it. There's something here as if everyone
The hair is black. I am enjoying it a lot.
I am feeling very comfortable. I
I am feeling very comfortable. I give
I will dance in front of you for hours.
I am feeling so good. But you just now
Get up and go like this. Get your hair golden
Go. I will start trembling. What should I do? Feet
Let me wash you and give you water to drink. I understand
I will not know how to behave brother.
[laughter] It is. And some girls are
Which gets light highlights done.
Under confident girls do not talk about them.
I have been.
Don't even talk about those who go to the parlor.
I have been. There are some girls who
[sound of throat clearing] bucket at home
Mixes colors in.
And puts her head in it. [Laughter]
Do you understand how many golden balls there are? Imagine
Are you guys able to do it? So at that party
Was also a Golden Ball girl. Deepanshu's
It seemed very close. Both danced once.
Were living. Was enjoying. I sit my
I was watching these people with the laminate. enjoy
I was doing it too. Then I saw that the
The golden boy girl whispered in Deepanshu's ear.
Said something. Pointed towards me. And then he
She started walking fast towards me. I
I looked back and saw a wall. [Laughter]
So the reference is towards me only. So I understand
I didn't know what to do. I quickly
picking. I took out my wallet and put it in my front pocket.
I kept it.
Oh, I can't trust this girl.
Yes, he is a thief, he is a pickpocket. [Laughter]
I see a suspicious person.
Let me hide my wallet first. [laughter] So
Take out your wallet and put it in your front pocket.
I took it and in the other hand I punched it.
Made it.
And it's coming fast. I am thinking
What will the conversation be? She's coming very close
Is. And I'm slowly raising my hand
Whatever she says, I will attack her directly.
Because I feel like he's coming to attack.
Has been. And as she started coming closer. They
She came closer to me saying Hi Shubham.
Gave a tight hug. And I'm completely defused
It happened in front of him. I hung like a corpse
On top of that. [laughter] And then my compliments
Bridges started coming. Shubham, you do stand-up.
Deepanshu told me about you. It
It's So Good That People Like You Are Following
Their passion. It was so nice of you to say
Together. Even I wanted to try something out
Out of the box. Yes. But we cannot do it
are. We got stuck in 9 to 5. a rat
Stuck in the race. Too much to get out of here
It is difficult. I am from all over India
Wanted to open a chain of makeup brands.
But we are not able to do it. but you
I see it and get very inspired. Very
I get motivated that someone has his passion.
I am following and at that time I made a video
etc. were also not included. when I was in college
When I had just started, I had so much experience in this art.
She was a big supporter and she was happy with this.
I thought, at least he is trying something. He
You didn't even see how much I laugh. Understanding
had been? [sound of clearing throat] very
Became happier. First time I stand
Someone made me feel so good about you.
I started feeling very good. I am very
I started feeling warm. Then Deepanshu came. We
All three started talking. Then this golden
Ba girl called. This is for 2 minutes
Went out. And I called Deepanshu
[sound of throat clearing] told him that brother
This golden boy girl of yours is so perfect.
Buddy. He is saying, brother, are you an idiot? Since when
This is the Golden Boy Girl Golden Boy Girl
He is speaking. This is blonde. [Laughter]
Now watch out if I don't stay open minded.
Yes, I would also say that yes brother is blonde.
These. But as he said, I got angry.
I have arrived. I said Deepanshu, any girl younger
Wears clothes.
She talks to everyone with a smile.
[Laughter]
The one whom the heart embraces
So he is bloody
[Appreciation]
[Cheers]
That is not blood, Deepanshu yes
Blondes are everybody [laughs].
who consider such girls to be blondes
We're All Blondes We Just Sell Different
Parts of Our Bodies
[Laughter]
Blood is just a profession.
The idiot is saying that hair is of black colour.
Of. [Laughter]
I said [ __ ]
I narrowly escaped. Yes. You understand
What a close encounter this was. [laughter] Okay.
That girl didn't have burgundy done.
My game was over [laughs] at that time brother. Me
Why did it feel so useless? I feel very guilty
I feel like I am open from the top.
I have become minded. But inside I
I am still very hollow. I have a lot of
Things need to be learned. I am very
I became conscious. I went home and the party was over.
But this thing kept going on in my mind.
Next day I went to college and called my girlfriend
Told everything. And some things would happen
are what you tell someone. And as soon as I tell you
I realise that it's [ __ ].
This should not be told. because like
I told her and she ran to bite me.
Is. Yes. Dude, are you crazy? These
You don't know all the basic things.
Blonde is a profession. [Laughter]
When will you learn all this, friend? been for two years
You live here in the big city. all these things
I don't know you. You come everywhere with your nose cut off
Are you leaving me? She is talking and shouting
It is upon me. Then he realized that he had made a mistake
It belongs to him. Are you saying you know what? I think
It is my fault. Maybe I got you right
Was not treated properly. you small town
You come from But I am from a big city.
You will come from your mother's womb with some knowledge.
All this. My responsibility is to you
Teach all this. your [ __ ] ups are my [ __ ]
Ups. Your mistakes are my mistakes.
I said yes.
Someone wants to take the blame on himself. Brother
I picked it up completely and kept it aside. [laughter] Then
He began to explain to me that you know what I will
Change you. I'll show you the ways here
I will teach you. I will introduce you to my friends. We
People will chill and go clubbing regularly.
Now the relationship has reached a good stage.
Was. She was also very serious. Me too
It was very serious. And with time I
I realized there was a huge gap.
In me and in him because my friend
In the circle you saw that the waiter was
Friends who call with tuberose in their pockets
friends who travel but his friend circle
In
lesbians were
And he never told me because
It is common for him. It is a very normal thing
For him. It is a festival for me.
[Appreciation]
This is a very big festival. I take leave
I can go home for this. [Laughter]
He told me the guest list and told me that I
I am leaving. You are walking. one of mine
Friend, Sonam is coming. And one of his also
A friend is coming. I am happy brother. That
Three girls and I alone in my circle
75% of the girls have never been there brother.
[Laughter]
75% of girls have never been
ever
We went clubbing and got too nervous.
I was thinking how I would break the ice which Sonam would do.
She was a friend and she broke the ice.
It is very easy to do it through stand up.
Breaking it, you just ask the comic
How much money do you earn and they start crying
[laughs]
So easily the ice breaks, he ice
We did breaks etc., we were a little jailed like this.
They upgraded it and then they started ordering.
Started eating and drinking and ordering
When I started doing it, I folded my hands.
that friend I don't drink so you
People should keep it a little non-alcoholic for me.
Do whatever you want for yourself, Sonam.
She was that type of girl, those are the types of girls.
No, when I talk, I feel like crying
Will take now
That
come on friend
[laughter] You didn't drink,
The party is organized for you all night long
We do all this for you.
Don't put restrictions on yourself while you live
Lose yourself, forget who you were
This is New You Pujari 2.0
I created a new version. How
Don't worry? We are not doing anything wrong like this
do. We Will Start With Something Light
And then we'll see where it goes. [Laughter]
So they ordered cocktails and
Coconut water was available. It was drinkable,
Coconut water was mixed in it. how do I know
All this? Because as soon as these people
I ordered that part and the tender started dancing.
He went in front of us. [Laughter]
He is tossing the coconut, breaking it,
Used to be. The coconut is tossing and breaking,
Is putting. I said, sisterfucker, go inside.
Make it, friend.
Why is everything happening in front of me [laughs]
Some? I bought a cocktail from the cart
What?
The big glass is for ₹30.
[Appreciation]
Splashes are falling on my face. Yes.
[Laughter]
The cocktail arrived. It was drinkable. Until I had a
These girls had drunk three or four drinks each.
I drank it repeatedly. Now I see
I have been here for half an hour. in the group
Something has started happening. girls
It is a little bit down. every little thing
She is celebrating. every little thing
Celebrating things. To the Night Va
Celebrated it the same night.
To the place that Jhatu celebrates the place
Gave. [Laughter]
To the New Guy.
Made me celebrate. [Laughter]
Now I also try to match their energy.
I am doing it. Because I only had one drink
I took it and I didn't get drunk at all.
I don't want to show it even a little bit
that their party is extremely boring and nonsense
Is. [laughs] I'm shaking a little bit.
And I'm wondering how long
Girls will keep faking. Now our people
The time has come.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Whatever one does in a party,
If you are having eye contact with someone else, then do all this.
I am giving it. [Laughter]
[applause] [cheering voice]
Whatever happens, it's all yours
I have gone proper after watching YouTube videos
How do you live [laughs].
And then suddenly Sonam looked at me happily and said wow.
You are having fun, no, we order beer.
I said yes, order it, definitely order it, those people
I ordered beer and it came in a bucket like this
[Laughter]
having a beer [sound of clearing throat] and
Now I have opened each lid in front of everyone.
I went with a cocktail mentality.
I picked up a bottle and took a sip.
people are among you who have ever
I haven't even tasted many beers.
People did not test, I will tell you guys
Tell me not to test at all.
should [laughs]
Because as soon as I took the first bite
I said, sisterfucker, I asked for your mouth.
These people.
[Appreciation]
My whole body started trembling, brother. Yes. it seems like
I have come home to pee. [Laughter]
Yes.
I noticed
that there is absolutely no trace of these girls' faces
There is no wrinkle while drinking it. so me
I had a little doubt, friend [laughs].
That I am a real man. If I use this
I am not able to bear the taste, so this
The girls should have fallen by now.
So do you guys understand what this means? Its
This means that the bottle that I have
It is expired.
[Laughter]
[Cheers]
I cracked it right. Yes, right crack.
Did. Open end shirt case. So I thought
How will you verify this? Own
I pick up the bottle containing the girlfriend. Test
I do. If the same test is coming then understand
I will go. So I looked into his eyes
Smiling at this. picked up his bottle and
Took a sip. I was very happy and said wow how
Romantic.
I said, of course, yes [laughs].
Only girls like petty things
yes brother
You can spoil their food, yes [laughs].
Feed one more before eating it yourself.
I don't know how people will say that they will fall there.
That girls have become very high maintenance
Is. I don't understand how people talk
Come. I think 3 feet of bare minimum
They want the things below.
[Laughter]
You make them do shopping worth Rs 500 in your name.
You will forget. Own
[sound of throat clearing] taking off the T-shirt
Give it to me. Yes, you will go crazy.
[Laughter]
Crazy [sound of clearing throat]
Will go. I will get your name engraved.
See how crazy girls get.
Regarding the T-shirt. Yes, I like your T-shirt
Needed I want a T-shirt. me tshirt
Needed Hey, I have four of them, brother.
Where can I get the T-shirt from?
[Cheers]
I picked up the kitchen cleaning t-shirt
Gave it.
[Laughter]
Even in that she is lying that wow it smells like
you are
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
I am smelling like turmeric. [Laughter]
I can smell the chutney inside me. What? Lie
So don't talk to me.
[Laughter]
So I picked up the bottle and tasted it. Beans
It's a test. [Laughter]
I understood that this is an acquired taste. These
People have been drinking it for a long time, so it
I am able to drink. If I took another sip
Then I will vomit. And whatever I have
I have built my own by doing everything. Yes I
[laughter] I'll vomit on him.
Now the night has become long. Yes. As long as the cocktail
The game was in my court. Now the beer has arrived.
Now I can't even refuse. are understanding
yes? A human being, a man, can never know all these things.
Can't even refuse. I can't speak
That I don't like the taste. Me
Give me pink underwear. I can't do all this.
Do you understand?
I will be looked upon with great respect.
[Laughter]
Now I realized I would have to use some trick.
I saw number five, these guys back.
Got absorbed in the conversation and disappeared. I
See, this is a good opportunity. I picked up the bottle and threw it away
Celebrate [sound of clearing throat]
Did it. I said to the night. They
And the eyes of all three girls sparkled.
Because I am a student of these people.
The eyes of all three sparkled. wow look who is
Having fun, I said,
And carrying the bottle, he swerved towards the dander
I went and said, brother [laughs] there's sugar in it.
Get it together friend
[Appreciation]
[Cheers]
I can't drink [laughs].
add some sugar
[laughter] Have you given it, brother?
I said one second one second one second
you would abuse me
you would have slapped me
But you chose to call me gay because you
It seems being gay is an insult, a curse if
Get out you bastard, don't talk nonsense
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
We don't have sugar, I said.
Put Gulab Jamun inside it, friend.
No Rasmalai left inside it, yes [laughs]
There is still some left that is drinkable.
He chased him away. I came to the table disappointed
I sat down. [Laughter]
Then Sonam and her friend got up. Both DJs
Went to. Both of them changed the music sense.
Got it done. Got some lighting changes done.
Both of them started dancing. both each other
Started coming near. And I, my girlfriend
I am sitting and watching. both of each other
Started coming closer. Both are hairy
Started touching.
And until I understand myself
Both of these
I kissed you, friend. and mine and my
The girlfriend had the same reaction. This
Bola va u go girls. And mine was, hey
Sisterfucker
[Appreciation]
What did these people do? [Laughter]
What if her boyfriend finds out?
And well, I have come with you. Yes.
[laughs] Otherwise you would have stuck with them too.
Are you saying you are crazy? Yes [laughter]
Why do I stick with them? and their
How will the boyfriend know? This is itself
There is a couple.
And don't you have a brain? So much
Everyone is shouting loudly, hey sisterfucker, at us.
Started watching. [Laughter]
The DJ turned off your music.
Hey sisterfucker. [Laughter]
Who stopped you? Hey, you sisterfucker, I said it.
Why do you get so expressive?
Pay? Think about all this in your mind. everywhere
Make me feel embarrassed. Look, the son is coming running.
Is. [Laughter]
Makes you feel embarrassed everywhere. yes. you had one
Job and that was to make them feel
Comfortable. And you have ruined the night.
Angrily she picked up her purse and went to the washroom.
Went. I am very much amazed. [Laughter]
Now I see everyone looking at me
because I've been really loud
Hey sisterfucker, you shouted. So I understand
I did not come, what should I do? Absolutely Conscious
I quickly picked up the bottle and gulped it down.
I gulped it down in one gulp. Test
It has been acquired.
Now a lot of thoughts are coming to my mind.
In. There are many feelings at once. I
I am very anxious. I am very much
I am scared. I am very nervous inside me.
But there's also a sense of achievement that
Hanging out with lesbians
I have been.
[Appreciation]
This is a very big thing for me. hey you guys
How do I explain? You think that you are doing it all day long
The ones you see in such laptops etc.
[Laughter]
[Cheers]
May he suddenly come out with you
You will not enjoy partying.
to the people
It's a big deal for me, my mind.
I had a lot of thoughts, I said something.
We have to make them feel good, make them feel welcome.
I want to get it done by calling him sisterfucker
The moment has spoiled me something good
I have to do it, there are a lot of thoughts going on that this
I can do it, I can do it, and so fast
Everything happened when both of them came back after dancing.
I didn't understand these people as soon as they
I came back, you guys won't believe I did both
touched the feet of
[Laughter]
I asked Ba Tender for a coconut. their feet
beneath
I passed the momos chutney that tika kar
Give me mine.
I am roaming around happily brother. Did a back flip.
I am moving in slow motion. Annual Function
I showed these people the Aarti. very big
It matters to me, doesn't it? It is a big thing.
I made a video call to my mother.
[Laughter]
Look who I am sitting with. And mommy too
I am happy that he is one of these.
Is anyone yours?
I said, hey, these people are not ladies.
These people are lesbians. Mummy is saying
Yes, this happens during the rainy season [laughs].
Some.
Tell me to drink hot water. I said hey friend
The mind is completely messed up there. Calls to friends
I guessed who I was sitting with.
[Laughter]
Guess who I am sitting with. Oh how is that
Should I guess? I said wild guess whose
I am sitting with you. What will be big for you?
talk? Yes, you do stand-up. Any
Must be sitting with a Bollywood actor. Any
Must be sitting with the director. With whom?
Are you sitting? Shahrukh Khan. I said no. Say
Salman Khan remains. I said no. Saying
Karan Johar. I said close [laughs] enough.
What are you saying? With whom?
Are you sitting? I said sister-fucking lesbian people
I am sitting with. [laughs] It would have been a bit real.
Is.
I said, I have touched it brother.
Well known name tested on quality.
[Laughter]
You people will not believe it. I was with them
The photo was taken like this.
[Cheers]
Like the one taken with the Taj Mahal.
Hey, these people are no less than monuments to me.
These are the people for this. These people are Mecca for me.
And there is Medina, brother.
When I was doing all this. So whatever your
Human vision sees 270°.
Is. As I'm doing this, I'm here
From here to here you will see 270° what is happening
Is. [Laughter]
So I noticed that at this angle
Our table is
Someone has been sitting there for quite some time.
[Laughter]
So when I turned around, I saw my
So, there is a girlfriend. He came quite some time ago
She is sitting there. [laughter] But he told me
Has not stopped. Yes, he let me
Is. That dog, you do it today. [Laughter]
You show your worth. Yes. you tell me you
What a mean man he is. But as soon as this
I did this, this is a very wrong thing.
Do you understand? [Laughter]
Never make someone feel welcome
This way. Many family members are forcing you to come home.
It is for the relationship. You go to your father-in-law
Took a photo like this with. [Laughter]
[Appreciation]
Those people will not come again. Yes. This is very
This is the only offensive thing. You are welcoming someone
To make them feel like this, take such photos of them.
[Laughter]
So as soon as I did this, my
The girlfriend came running from there. my collar
caught. She dragged me out. I
I saw both my Taj Mahals getting smaller.
Are.
And he went out and pushed me.
Are you crazy? what is all this
Are you doing it inside? Yes. touched their feet
Of the people. [laughter] Feet breaking coconuts.
Below yes? Mummy ko video call lage me
Have you come here? [Laughter]
You make me feel embarrassed everywhere. Yes. every
Place Embarcade. A small town boy always
Will be from a small town. no matter how much he
Try painting it. your fault
Not that you came here. My fault that I
I have brought you here. people coming and going
I am laughing at you. Yes. you on
I feel ashamed to do it. I love you
I feel ashamed to walk with you.
[Laughter]
I started to feel so useless that I
whoever came
[Laughter]
I did everything.
How could everything go wrong? [Laughter]
How will I grow in life? Yes. These
They say you touched my feet wrongly.
What a wonderful coconut you broke.
So I will know that the coconut one is repeating
You have to do it, don't do the action of touching the feet.
Then I will be a better person next time.
everything is wrong. I should jump from here then.
Yes.
What is all this you are saying? What is all this?
You are roaming around with chutney on your face. Yes.
[laughter] Go wash your face. Come back after washing your face.
I became sad. My head is spinning, it's night
Has been. Everyone disowned me. Disone what?
Meaning I was insulted. I thought the people inside
I am enjoying myself, that's why I am laughing. They
People were laughing at me. I am very ashamed
Is. Yes, I went stumbling somehow.
It happened in the washroom and it was a very shady place. You
People must have gone clubbing etc. that shady bit
There is a place. I went inside. Washed my mouth,
Took face wash, washed mouth and filled mouth
I started burning. I thought the sisterfucker chutney spilled
Went.
A man was washing his face nearby. I
Where is brother?
Brother, my mouth is burning.
He is saying, brother, did you wash your face with phenyl?
Is.
[Laughter]
I said brother, what should I do?
He is saying, brother, you go away. [Laughter]
I have been watching you for an hour.
You are doing something inside.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
You broke their tiles along with the coconut.
Have given.
You go away or you will return naked.
[Laughter]
I called my friends and said, brother
I am stuck here. come and take me
Go. Kabav [throat clearing sound]
Bring me anything quickly from here
Take it out. My friends came and I went out.
Went. I messaged them that from my house
The call is coming. I have to leave. It's
Very late. Waited for half an hour. My friend
Come [sound of clearing throat]
By sitting in an e-rickshaw.
Four friends.
His idea was that I would sit in the front.
[Laughter]
These are my friends. Yes. And they would come too
Every time where is the lesbian
[Appreciation]
There are two girls behind me waiting for a cab.
I said, are you guys lesbians?
Brother
[laughter] Come on, come on, the police are coming here.
The police are coming [laughter]
We travel in our rickshaw
My friend's phone rang tiding
Ting Tiding Hello
[Laughter]
Ting Tding Hello
[sound of throat clearing] I went home three or four
I felt very guilty that day, yes I
I was ashamed to call these people.
I also did not call back people
I messaged Sonam who was her friend.
Did he ask for number one on Instagram?
I called him and said, friend, sorry, that day I
These people had done too much
lesbians have you guys ever hung out
Someone with lesbians, these people are very
We live above people mentally who are more
is also bisexual lesbian because you
Look, people are not accepting their weight.
I am unable to accept my color
Cannot accept his height.
But accept your sexuality.
Take. That too when they are a complete minority.
The whole society is laughing at you.
It is a very bold thing. accept this
Take. So she would have been mentally much above us.
Is. Like I called him and said sorry friend
That day I did a little too much. Me
I don't want to [throat clearing sound]
Was. I was drunk. So someone is saying yes
No matter. Oh, we forgot. we were having
Fun. And of course you were drunk. Someone Real
He won't do all this in life.
[Appreciation]
[Laughter]
I said of course
Why would anyone do this in real life?
[Laughter]
My girlfriend infact is older than me.
She remained angry till then gradually she also came along.
She got onboarded and then we were together.
We started roaming around and we became a group.
These people started going here and there regularly.
New openings used to teach me the ways
Went to town to make minded yes fine
Dining and so on were carried everywhere and
When I get to hang out with them regularly
I felt like I learned a lot of things.
I learned from living with them that if a
If there is base in the boy's voice then some girl
He might even snatch her mangalsutra [laughs].
So girls find it cute. Did you see it?
Base boys, yes that's us.
Can I buy your drink yes clubbing and so on
These people are found in Yes, Hey, Can I
By your drink and the girls are completely confused
It happens that hey
You came with your husband [laughs], brother, yes
How are you even thinking? Yes [laughs] you see.
These people say two words, yes,
Honestly
Perhaps
Ask me anything, honestly, I have asked for your name.
your brother
[Appreciation]
[Cheers]
What is your name? Is it Ramesh or Prakash?
Jyoti, what's your name [laughs]
what are we doing
You saw the boys with the bass, those thin ones.
Chibillians are in every group [laughs].
That we're honestly worried [laughs]
Raghu played Holi
I saw these boys if girls
If the mangalsutra is also snatched away, the girls will be shocked.
Looks cute. Dude, did you hear his voice?
Heard his voice. How well he treated me
Snatching the mangalsutra, he called her sister's [ __ ].
[Laughter]
[Appreciation]
Did you see the guys on the base? Yes? Dod
We speak words
This is the voice of a real man
I've been talking for an hour like a bedbug [laughs].
I am in front of you people, yes, someone from someone
Don't be ashamed, speak as God has sent you.
Yes, is the vibrator stuck in my throat?
You have [laughs] yes
Yes, you are running on battery.
I think about these two bases
Where would the boys be talking about us?
You are not even expressing yourself in front
Expression of a person is also important. Where
Do those people talk? So I realized
I said that these guys with bass, two basses
Boys talk hiding behind such trees
Must be doing it. [Laughter]
hey humstly
Honestly [laughs]
But
Hey, what's up, they caught me.
The people. [Laughter]
Now I am a sisterfucker, honestly.
I am being told. But I am saying sister
of. [Laughter]
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
You can pull them and slap them anytime.
His and my voice will be the same. anytime
Try it. Look, that relationship is very
It is special.
in which you
virginity
and self-respect
[Laughter]
You lose both of them. Self-Respect
I was losing from day one. [Laughter]
You people must have seen it. Now the time has come
Her virginity was gone. Now on my mind
There was no timeline as such. Relationship
I had reached a good stage. three four
It had been years since we started dating. Now
I was under social pressure to have sex.
Of. [Laughter]
Yes, my friends are in the semester.
Failing to get me to have sex.
[Laughter]
Yes, because whenever we met, all these things happened.
There used to be talks.
If he still doesn't do it, the girl will become impotent.
She will understand you. [Laughter]
The whole college will spit on you. The world will laugh
On you. People will say that they got the hand but not the mouth.
Put.
I will write outside your gate, write small
Why disappointed? I said it's done brother. yes
Went.
I will go to the side just now. I went to my
to my girlfriend and we mutually
Decided that we will do it.
Why am I lying to you people?
[Laughter]
Not mutually decided. I
pleaded.
I begged for sex. Yes. Because
People who are in relationships know that such
I have to beg or do something strange
You have to use it. Only you people know this
will be. But from my experience, I
I will tell you what I learned, if you look at it
One has to beg for sex. So plum
It is minimum. [Laughter]
But if you have to beg for sex
So ask in English. [Laughter]
What happens with that? Your intentions are very
They come out pure. for some reason
[laughter] And all the risky words
They get eliminated.
She will take as she gives.
[Appreciation]
inside out yes
Back and forth. Without using all these words, if
If you have sex, you will give girls a
So you look like a Mahatma type. So I am complete
I went after reading the article etc. I
I had gone after learning it by rote. I went
Near this. I said see even I am
Against the Idea That We Should Do It Before
Marriage. [Laughter]
I Can Live With You Forever Without Even
Touching you if that's what you want.
But
[Laughter]
According to this article on fog.
It Says If You Don't Have a Physical Relationship
For a very long time, it may lead to lower
Self-Esteem
Lower Self-Confidence
Poor heart health [laughs]
Poor prostate health, yes, Google it.
This is how Google tells you that you are in two minutes.
If you don't have sex inside, you're dead.
will go
Get it done now, yes I can't find anyone.
Boys, boys, do it amongst yourselves [laughter].
So after saying all this I told her not to have sex
Told about the disadvantages. Now anyone should be emotionally
Triggering is a very easy thing in the world.
Look, everyone thinks that his friend is in his life
I am not the same as before. Yes. 2019
Before that, he was doing something crazy. Now their
There is no comeback. The downfall has arrived.
Yes. [Laughter]
I have never been on top.
Always waiting for my comeback [laughs]
Are. Hey, your comeback is happening every day brother.
You don't know, you just come back
You do it and you reach the same level
[laughter] How do you know everyone?
It seems everyone thinks that my friend
There's a lot going on in life, but I
I don't let it come on my face, not on my face
Let me come, I am facing a lot.
Just bring a smiling face in your life
I am fooling the world that is true
It's the same with you, it's the same with you
But it happens with everyone, so I have discussed this thing.
used
To trigger him emotionally, I
said but I don't care what this article
Since I know that there is a lot going on in
Your personal life. Now I'm guessing
with everything that is going on in your
Family [laughs]
Between you and your sister. I know I know she
Is a [ __ ], yes.
[laughter] You don't tell me these things, but I
Can See It in Your Eyes Lately. It's on your
Face. Yes, because I am yours all day long
I just keep looking at the eyes.
You will find many people who will say
Are the first girl that they have loved. you are the
First Girl That He Ever Loved. But for me
You are the last girl that I will ever love.
[Appreciation]
The Only Girl That I Will Love More Than You Is
Probably our daughter in the future.
And as I said all this, I turned back.
I saw that he had taken off his clothes.
[Appreciation]
[Laughter]
So the first sex is very awkward.
I am telling all this for the boys.
Yes. Because whatever girls spoil
Yes, it normalizes it. [Laughter]
The boy thinks that I am the fool
Am.
[Laughter]
So I'm telling you guys, boys.
so that you guys can know better about yourself
Feel it because I am very happy with the first second.
It is awkward. I already during
I was so happy [laughs].
That I had epilepsy.
So at first he thought of doing role play also.
It was stuck.
[laughs] Then when he understood it, he
Within seconds the girl is hitting me with her shoe.
Yes. threw cold water on me
Sisterfucker, don't die naked in my room.
[Laughter]
[sound of clearing throat]
Now I will tell you the truth if you ask me the truth.
I am against bisex.
[Laughter]
I don't think there should be sexwax.
There is a difference of only 19-20. are you with someone
Or be alone. So the difference is only 19-20. But
People have hyped up sex so much.
that your brain gets a boost that
But if I look at it fun wise, it is only 19-20.
There is a difference. And comes with lots of baggage
It's sex. Sex doesn't come alone. to the people
It seems that the freest of the free in a relationship
I never do, brother. You always pay a
Price for it. Yes. [laughs] Sex never
He doesn't come alone. Sex comes in flocks.
Like a pig.
Yes. Because look what the boys are up to.
Let's do sex like sex. did and
Forgot. [Laughter]
Girls do it like an event.
That I helped some poor person.
A farmer was put into debt.
like an event, like a charity
Brother, this one. And I think of the girls' POV.
So there is a charity that is being done for us.
Is. Because it is not possible for us brother.
[Laughter]
You can laugh, he cannot become a brother to boys. You
Look how filthy these boys live.
They live so unhygienic. Is my friend.
He lives with so much filth. his girlfriend
When she comes to meet him, the black heat is upon her
She beats. [Laughter]
She is going to meet him. bathing in acid
He is at home. Yes. rubbing with sandpaper
To myself. Napthalene under her arm
Trapped the ball.
It should not be infested with insects. [Laughter]
Hey, they put the cargo in the quilt.
And a very emotional bond is formed. sex
After such emotionally very connected
You become it. Fights start a lot
Is. And I saw the girls fight every now and then
There is a loop hole. It's called mood
Swings.
Yes, God has given it to these people. [Laughter]
So at most I would have ignored the fight.
I thought, friend, this is a job that requires a lot of effort.
But one fight I saw was very easy.
I thought this fight would end immediately.
I can easily win in two or three lines. So
I almost proved it wrong.
I almost took it as LHS equal to
RHS proved it and also accepted that
I accept that it is my mistake, Shubham.
It's a mistake. But have you ever tried to know
Why did I make this mistake?
[sound of clearing throat]
I said because you are a number one ignorant person.
And you are an illiterate girl.
I don't want to say that my periods had come, Shubha. But
Thank you for showing me your true colors.
I said, sisterfucker, how did you lose here?
Dude, me?
[Appreciation]
This was a battle I had won, brother.
[Laughter]
How did I lose from here, friend? I absolutely
It started feeling like BJP of Ayodhya.
[Appreciation]
How from here
I started to notice a pattern [laughs]
Whenever something is messing up its mood
The swings are coming. So I had a
There is a tracker app. The period tracker app was
That was installed. He felt Shiva.
[Laughter]
[Appreciation]
I said of course
I did it for myself [laughs]. My
Video games are available from today.
[Laughter]
Now I started tracking her periods. Now
I'm noticing a lot of mood swings.
It is coming to this. Once such similar type
There was a fight. She also accepted that it was her mistake. I
I admit it was my fault this morning. have you ever
Tried to find out. My mood swings
They went. That's why I did all this. Address
[sound of clearing throat] mood swings
How do I feel? i feel like
Let me eat ice cream. when eating ice cream
I seem to be gaining weight. I
I told you to get your brain treated.
[laughter] Why are you putting it on periods?
For him? Yes.
You will never understand. you know how many
There are more hormonal changes in the body
In. How many geopolitical changes
There are.
How many National Geographic changes?
They are present in the body. on top of that you
Every battle has to be won. each argument
I have to win. I don't know what you will do
By winning the argument. I said [laughter] Grandpa
Don't shout. Your period is over 13
It's been days.
Without periods, there are no mood swings.
I have also read this much bio.
Say you have read so much bio. so to you
You might also know about PCOD.
My periods can come at any time.
Can go. I said keep it, you sisterfucker.
You guys.
I don't want to fight, brother. Yes.
Now you see how many girls
He is privileged brother.
These people will murder and call one to court.
Times. They are saying Chaku is gone, Judge Sahib. Yes.
You are after me, yes. To you
Do you know what mental state I was in? Yes.
What was going on in my mind? You pen
Take the paper and make it a serious business. pen
Keep it first.
[Laughter]
There is so much privilege that by murdering
We will call them to court and even then they will be punished once.
The law will let you know that yes, she is right.
Is. [Laughter]
God made something for us boys.
No, brother. I didn't make anything brother. You
If you commit murder, you will have to go to jail. you go
I cannot speak in court in my peace.
The penis got stuck so I did it
[Cheers]
[Applause] I can't say it at all.
I have been [laughs]
You can't say anything at all, you will be punished.
I'll slap you a couple of times separately [laughs]
Sisterfucker, he has committed murder and is also an idiot.
[Laughter]
I can't say everything bro.
Look, there comes a time in a relationship when
One of the two realizes
that oh [ __ ]
We have no future at all.
O!
This should have been discussed on day one.
But never mind, it's been 5 years, you could have done it today.
Are. [laughs] So in my relationship
The time had come. One day she suddenly started crying.
Saying I Don't Think We Have a Future
Together. Then I started crying after hearing this. This much
Open your purse and juice will come out, sister [laughs].
So I calmed down a bit and asked
How much time do you have left [laughs]
I mean, [laughs]
I told you you have cancer.
You smoke cigarettes [laughs] I'm narrow-minded.
Do you understand that you are crazy, I don't
think this is working out why I did what
[sound of clearing throat] It's done. Now!
So everything was fine. Can I Was Skeptical
About It From a Very Long Time. Me
It's been a while since I've felt like Initial Day.
It was not happening. Feels like initial time
It was not happening. Then I thought that
It will be temporary, but it is quiet some month now.
And I still feel the same way. So
I told my friends and my
Friends said tell him the truth
if you or if you without feeling
Even if you are in a relationship, you are cheating.
It is counted.
[sound of clearing throat] I said Sean
Don't create.
Don't create a scene. Don't create a scene.
She is saying that this scene is not even being created.
There are only two of us sitting in the room.
I said let's work. I got my job
It was there at that time. I said let's do one thing.
The salary has arrived, let's go on a trip. I am saying
Don't think we should meet anymore.
I said let's do one thing, let's take a break
Are. I had already seen Friends by then.
I knew you could take a break.
Yes, relationship. But there is a reason for this because
I am not preparing for the conversation right now.
I have come. I have come to eat food. Little
I will get time. If this too stays a little far away
You will understand and realise it. I said
Let's take a break. say you can try
Whatever you want. But I don't think this is
Going to work out. Then he said and went home
Went.
I started feeling very useless. I went home
I started feeling like a patient.
How many of you have ever
Have you had a breakup? Yes, ma'am, tell me when did it happen?
Is your breakup?
three days ago.
three days ago
And how long was your relationship?
Two years.
You did it for two years. He did.
[nasal sound]
Both did it because after two years
Realized that we don't have a future
Together.
Okay, okay. To those who have happened to
I know there is an emotional pain along with it.
There is also a physical pen. You are very patient
Typing starts to feel heavy. I so
I went home and I didn't feel like doing any work.
doing. I can't talk to anyone
I am not able to do any work, am I?
I am saying something to someone.
This is what happens when the first phase of a relationship
What happens is fictional fuzz. in that you
They roam around happily like idiots. a girl
100 bad things happen in your life.
It starts to feel good. But the same girl
When the boy leaves you. 100 good
Things start to feel bad to you. you to sleep
You are sitting in a palace but you think you are
You are sitting covered in polythene. And I so
I am a bit of an uncle type.
[sound of clearing throat] I am just a body
get left. Will Tao sisterfucker be coming?
Yamraj now. [Laughter]
After so much suffering, will anyone survive?
Then it is over. Feeling very heavy
Had been. 10-15 days passed. I thought that now
Something has to be done. How long will I remain in this darkness?
I will keep going. I Googled me
What should be done? So Google said that you
Don't keep it inside you. You will keep it inside you
It will become poison. It will spread throughout your body.
You should share this with people. as much as you
The more you tell me, the more light you will feel. I said
It is a fact. It's been 15 days since someone
There is no clue. Because I also give examples
You give me the relationship. That
[nasal sound] relationship
So be it. Yes. How to go right now
Should I tell you the news of the breakup? Yes. Do you understand?
So I called my friend. Our
Deepanshu is my friend. called him to
Brother, it is like this. She is asking for a breakup
Is. I have convinced myself to take a break.
She is saying that she doesn't feel the same as before.
Friends can remain as they are. Said brother, look
Let me tell you one thing straight from the 100, girls.
who needs sex
And you might not be able to have sex.
[Laughter]
I was feeling useless. feeling bad
Was.
[Cheers]
Google told me this after asking Yahoo.
[Laughter]
I remained sitting listening. Vomit
[throat clearing sound] Straight thing going
It stuck in my mind. Two minutes later, he called again.
Went after two minutes. He is saying that brother Pandey is also there.
On call.
We want to know what your little one is.
What?
I said, brother, don't call me for two-three months.
to do.
I am blocking you guys.
[Laughter]
Cut it in this manner for another 10-15 days. then felt
That enough has been broken. It's been a month
Is. I need clarity now or I
Got closure. I will move ahead in life. Or
So it is also the Day of Hope, who knows now a
He must have realised it within a month. Yes
I will go and talk to you. So I bought a gift
Took. Called this one. We did it twice
Cut it off. I did it five times and it cut me off.
Then he stopped picking it up. 15 times
Went. It's 25. 35 45 55
Then I felt that I was busy.
Hey, I am also this mature. Yes. You
Are people not mature? Yes. [Laughter]
You thought I would discuss it at home.
Nearby, 10 minutes away. I went like this
Home. I rang the bell. Our common from inside
The friend who turned out to be Ishaan.
He asked, what is he doing here? you are saying
What are you doing here? They came from behind. Say
What are you doing here? I said
I was here for some time now. Now!
I went there a while ago. what are you doing here
Used to be? We
say [sound of clearing throat] ever since our
There has been a breakup. I said we broke up
Is. We are on a break. say break then
It is in your mind, isn't it? from my side
So the breakup has happened. I said since when
We have broken up. I used to cry a lot
Am. I remain very worried. I am very
I remain sad. I don't understand I
What should I do? And today I hit my lowest.
I didn't understand I have been since morning
I was feeling suicidal. So He Just Came
Here to make me feel comfortable.
[sound of clearing throat]
I said Ishaan is my brother.
I am also [ __ ].
[Laughter]
I keep crying all day long.
I don't understand what to do?
Please make me feel comfortable.
How will you do it? You must be hugging. you cuddle
Will do it. Do you kiss on the forehead? you have
Some have taken a diploma, some are comfortable
No [laughs].
come here give me a hug ishaan or dude you are
making it so uncomfortable do please make pee
Will comfortable Ishaan come here give me hug saying
dude step away dude dude you're stepping on
I said please give me a hug, someone told me
Pushed, pulled and slapped, hey
Sisterfucker, this is what keeps happening with you guys.
She also keeps telling me that you are mine too
He says, is this my job, sisterfucker?
[Laughter]
I picked up my bag from the sofa and made my way downstairs.
Got down. Whatever phones these people make, yes
Call this Holi Raghuveeravali [laughs]
And this girl started shouting at me.
How can you slap the [ __ ] out of him, man?
He just came here to help me out, yes, and
You don't understand what you don't understand
I feel like I was before
I was honest with you, now I don't feel it
You seem like a wall
I don't get any feeling when I look at the wall.
I don't get any feelings when I see you
You don't understand what you think
Will you give me a break of 15 days like this?
You will give me a month's break and everything will happen.
Change, will you call me 50 times? I will
Change my mind. Hey, this thing is not infused.
Can be done. You understand. you try it
You can bring me back to Singh Lala by doing that when
It will not come from within me.
As long as I was there, I was with you honestly.
Do You Want Me to Fake It? yes do you want
Me too fake it?
[Laughter]
I said yes.
Do whatever you want to do. It should become like the old one. You
You are crazy. you don't understand
What happened. Any man at this point would have
Left me and gone. But inside you
You are ashamed, you don't understand.
What are you doing.
[sound of clearing throat]
I am starting to feel very bad. Very
I started feeling very bad, meaning this
Come and give me anything in this world, you people
You come and tell me, it doesn't matter to me at all.
But [sound of clearing throat] girl
I can't say it, friend. You look at the relationship
How much should you go out of your way for your partner?
You do things for Above your friends
You prioritize it. your parents
You fight with You think this, not your family members
If you agree, you will run away. But when those same people turn
They go and turn against you. So it
Is the most hurtful feeling in the world.
I started getting very angry. I
said give me one reason why are you doing
Dec. And I'll make sure I never will
Call you again. I'll Make Sure You Will
Never get to see my face again. As soon as he hears
She started crying. Then she calmed down. Then he
Told you that you are a good boy. I
Said I know that.
[laughter] But the problem is that you
You are a little too good.
You have no opinions of your own
Are. If I said left, you would turn left.
yes. If I say right, you become right.
You are like kneaded dough.
I understood what had happened.
[sound of clearing throat] [laughter]
Now I am not getting angry. I feel
If something is not going on like this, I will leave. Me
I want to say something hurtful. have to say something like
Which makes him feel guilty. to know this
He must have done wrong to me. This is
Probably the last time speaking to her. Yes,
After this we probably did not have any conversation.
Saying something that hurts him
Always makes me feel guilty and I am standing here.
I also planned a lot of things.
I will say that this relationship
Was the best part about my life. But now
That you are going like this. This has become the
Worst Part About My Life. Everything
I have brought it after memorizing it. I want to say everything.
I'm feeling a bit very angry.
But I couldn't say anything to him
Front. I felt that I should feel guilty about this.
Don't have to give. My father once told me
I never felt guilty about a man leaving.
Should not be given.
[sound of clearing throat]
When I was in 10th, my grandmother's lungs
They had gone bad. She used to smoke a lot. So
So yes, I used to drink it regularly. So we them
He was taken to the hospital and the doctors saved him.
To them in some way. But he said this a lot
It is critical. Now she'll smoke again.
So we won't be able to save her. So keep n
Eye on her. We went home with grandmother. 7
For eight months, Grandma was very clean and absolutely
We were also careful. then suddenly
He doesn't know what happened. He neighborhood
By giving such money to the child, he is put in chains like this.
Got it. And for three, four, five days she was
Smoking and no one found out one day
It suddenly collapsed and took everyone
They ran to the hospital because of my boards.
There was an exam and we were home after two-three days.
The renovation was going on in a chaotic manner.
The atmosphere was such that everyone went to the hospital and the doctor
I replied that we won't be able to save her.
Papa said, still you should get him treated.
I will definitely try from my end.
All the money in the house was on him.
I invested Rs 10-15 lakhs in two-three days.
Grandmother regained consciousness inside and after two-three days
He came and as soon as grandmother regained consciousness she said that
Keep ₹13500 in my box.
If the treatment would take that much, I would think
Give. [Laughter]
It cost ₹15 lakh. [Laughter]
And Papa said, hey, I am busy with the treatment.
It is ₹6000. Why are you getting worried? And all
People got angry with Papa and said, hey Papa
Why didn't you tell grandma? they know
So let's go, he did something wrong. Yes. For them
You should have made him realise this. Father
He said, look, grandmother left after two-three days.
Will go. And I don't want those two or three
Live the day with the guilt that they did wrong
Have done. When a man does wrong to you
So he already feels guilty. One
It is human nature. Feeling guilty a lot
It is a basic thing. Everyone feels all this. When
A man who does wrong to you, he does it himself.
There is a self-realization that he is guilty.
Is. Don't make it worse by telling him.
do it. Never let any departing person feel guilty.
Should not be given. By telling them the truth
There is no benefit of it. Everyone's ego is satisfied
It will happen. So I also remained standing there.
I could not say anything to him. I all
He had taken some things away after beating me. I
I just stood there. telling you to say something
Not there.
[sound of clearing throat] I said mine
There is some stuff lying at your house. I
I will come and take it next week. Just saying you came
Why were they? [sound of clearing throat]
I said I thought everything would be fine.
But I don't think, now looking at it I don't think so
Something is going to be alright. And having said this, I
He started descending the stairs like this. It stopped me from
If you want, we can be friends.
Are.
I said, brother, I am not friends with you.
Will get it. Then I go back and watch my friend for a while
I will become. Then [laughter] I went up two or three more stairs.
Came down. Then she stopped me saying a
Go while explaining the matter.
Am I Making a Mistake?
I said a girl like you can never make a
Mistake.
[Appreciation]
After a breakup, you go through a phase.
Face with moving on. Yes, what to do with it
I don't even know what it is. How many people you
Among the people who are just moving on
Are. If you don't raise your hand, you'll look very useless.
You. [Laughter]
Because you broke up three days ago.
Is. Yes, and there is someone else besides them who
[sound of clearing throat] Okay, the rest of you.
So they don't even believe it.
Yes, no, people are not able to move on. Brother
I just had a show somewhere in Banaras or Lucknow.
A boy was sitting in the front row. He Said
That brother, I have been moving on for five years.
Am. [Laughter]
I said brother, the government changes every 5 years.
I asked how big your relationship was.
saying relationship
[laughs] I met her at my brother's wedding.
I said he knows you [laughs].
I am telling him this one-sidedly, not even this.
I know I am.
I said go ahead brother. Yes. I also stand
Is. Came. I didn't know how to move
Have to turn it on. I was just thinking that now
How to proceed further. I don't see anything in life
Used to be. [sound of throat clearing] Sonam's
The call came. His friend called him.
Went. That hello how are you? She so high
asked Energy. I forgot that my
My ass is torn. [Laughter]
I said I am fine.
She is saying that we should meet in the evening today. I said
No.
I said no, I don't feel like it. Then what
Done. I said you must know
Everything. If I say yes then breakup etc.
It keeps happening, friend. What's in it? Ahead
Go ahead. I said [sound of clearing throat]
It is easy for you to say everything.
[Laughter]
Saying the Relationship Was Just a Part of Your
Life. It Was Not Your Entire Life. I
What do you know about losing a girl?
Sadness.
She is saying it well. Who would know better than me
This thing?
I am the best. better than you guys
I can understand this thing. and very long
It's life, brother. It is a very big world. Very
There are many opportunities. a lot of people
I will meet you. a lot of girls
Will meet. You will find many boys. Yes.
Who knows, you might also be bisexual. [Laughter]
I said, don't say all this even as a joke. You
What people say comes true.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Are you saying you are crazy? [Laughter]
Which people does this happen to? of us
Things are not true. [Laughter]
I said, tell me what should I do?
Is? I don't understand everything. So he
Told two-three things how to move on.
I also learned something from my own experience.
Learned. I will tell you guys. Look Move On
There are only three steps to do it. you guys
[nasal sound]
Am. It is very easy. The first is that you breathe
Have to stay. [Laughter]
This is a very important step. only then
Both steps will work.
Secondly, you should turn around and get back at your ex.
Don't call your partner. Message
Don't do it. try to contact
I won't do it because you are in a relationship like this.
You move in centimeters. Someday 2
cm Some day 3 cm. someday
Well done 5 cm. But you back
You go in kilometers. [laughter] that you have a
Called 6 km. Went back. Now back
Have to start from. Yes, and the third one is very
The important step is that you should do this one day at
A time-consuming process that I've done for myself
It was very helpful. One day at a time
Process that you can plan your day like this
You have to take it so that you do not face any problem today. Today
Make your day so busy that you don't have time.
Didn't find it. Like you have a passion. To you
I like running. Do you like to play badminton?
Is. You like going to the gym. Prime you
I want to become a minister. whatever you like
[laughter] It is. You work behind it. As
I used to do stand-up. Me and Regressively
Started doing stand-up. I go to the open mic every day
I started leaving. I didn't feel like it. Then
I'm also going to open mics. from people
I am talking so that I can stay at home.
Strange things will go through my mind.
And hang out with random people. Yes.
Call anyone by putting a call wall and chatting
Do it together and pass the time. random [ __ ]
Pass the time with. I am my friends
I have old friends whom I have never met before
Was not there. I am calling him and saying, your brother
I got a missed call 6 years ago. [Laughter]
You had just come to Delhi. I am taking a bath
Was.
Tell me what happened? See you this evening. Saying
Brother, I have come to Nagpur.
I will meet you in Delhi in my next life.
Now he has a very vulnerable face. brain in it
You will get a lot of ideas in this. yes that
I do one thing, I call a girl and abuse her.
I will give it to you. Go to his house and create a scene.
I give. Girls will also feel that begging
I will ask for it. somehow beg him
Let me stop it. But at that time, you
You will do it and you will also feel like a winner.
It must be that friend, I have ruined my relationship
Worked very hard to save. But you 5 6
When you look back after a month, you will
I will feel very guilty that I am a sisterfucker
I am blocked on Instagram and WhatsApp.
I am blocked. I understand sisterfucker Paytm
[Laughter]
Yes, it is a small black and white app.
who has blocked me
[laughter] You'll see another face move.
Any idea to turn it on?
He doesn't have to take action in your mind.
Any idea comes to your mind, do one thing, one trick
I'll tell you to get a sock and lick it properly.
Okay, by licking it and wearing it and shoes
put my foot in
[nasal sound]
Now no idea will come to your mind.
Now you will remain like this all the time sister, what is it?
[applause] [cheering] Hey
No no, I am like this. sex comes and goes
You will reject it. Hut [laughs]
Oh no, Janhvi Kapoor, get out of here.
[Applause] Listen, your mind will be blown. you at night
You will fall asleep tired. No idea will come
In your mind. You do a lot of things
You can. Like you can change your place.
You can change jobs so that you get a
Get a fresh perspective on life. So I
Earlier one used to work in Noida. my job
It had started. I told them, you guys
I don't even know the work you give me.
And I think very hard and do it this way
I give. I can't do it. and right now
There are a lot of things going on in my personal life.
Has been. So I just want to log in.
Doesn't do. But I live in a big city
I am staying. So is my cost of living.
Is. So you can do this for some time.
What if you just give me salary?
[laughter] And when I get better, I'll do a little
I will compensate by doing extra work. Say
I can't leave anymore. [Laughter]
You guys fired me from my job. I
I was on a break for two-three months until I
Won't I get a little better? Then such a one day
Through the at-time process, I gradually
It went out. I never even called back
I did it, but didn't even message. It's Been Too
Years more than two years now. And then when
I started feeling a little better after 5-6 months.
I found a job. I first
Used to live in Noida. I want to take a job in Gurgaon
I thought my location should also change. Job
There should also be a change. Went to work on the first day. very much
Fun incident happened. Went to work on the first day. They
Orientation program etc. is the job
In. Do you guys know?
Yes.
How many of you do job-wap?
From? Yes. So on the first day they paused.
We give you training in the office. [Laughter]
You know, you guys know about pose training.
Is? Yes. There is someone who doesn't know the pose
What happens is this.
Raise your hands like this, there is nothing to be ashamed of.
Is. You don't know, brother, you don't know
Is. You don't know. ok whoever
I don't know, like you don't know, brother.
Let me tell you. Look at all the things you
Runs in the mind.
[Laughter]
All that comes in posh. Yes. [Laughter]
I think Posh's training design too
It was done like this. that a girl must have come and
You must have asked the boy what's going on with you.
In the mind?
You remain lost the whole day. someone [laughs]
Don't tell anything to anyone. looking up into the sky
You keep smiling. And the boy said I
I want this to happen, sisterfucker. Let this be it
Lets do it. And the girl must have noted everything and
He must have written 'Posh' on top and torn it, saying that from today onwards
Nothing will be possible. So you can go to any office
I go. Give you a training
Posh's training. That's the kind of training that
that some of the normal things that you
It may seem normal, but it is sexual harassment.
It counts in . Prevention of sexual
That is called harassment. like you are someone
Girls should not be touched inappropriately like this.
You can do it. don't compliment him
You can. Don't comment on her clothes
You can. You can't ask him out.
Netflix and chill at my place. Not all of this
You can do it. [Laughter]
Many more pointers were written. one two then
I had written nonsense that you should treat a girl like this
You can't ping on the wall. [Laughter]
Who would be such a boy?
The one who will say that friend, I am a compliment
I don't give.
Sometimes I just pin it on the wall.
And then I wrote one last pointer which made me
I completely disagreed. It was written in it that
You Can't Indulge in Any Kind of Sexuality
Activity in this office premises. I
Said Sir I have one doubt. They say get up
Get up introduce yourself. Sir, I
said sir my name is Shubham Pujari say hi
Shubham. So happy to have you on board. Or
Tell me what is your doubt? I said Sir,
The Last Point Is Where It Says You Can't
Indulge in any kind of sexual
Activity in this office premises. without
Consent.
I [laughs] think these two words are missing
There.
Say Shubham that is very funny. See Bee It
Consensual beat non-consensual you can't
Indulge in any kind of sexual
Activity in this office ruminates. I said
Sir, you understand. [sound of clearing throat]
I am ready. Yes. [Laughter]
The girl in front is ready. Then do it
Can. Shubham you are waking it up very much
Awkward. [Laughter]
Anybody Else Has This Doubt Here. He has the most
I asked and no one raised their hand. someone
Did not raise his hand. I can say with certainty
Yes, 70% of the people will have that doubt. But this is
There is a difference. A confident man has a
Under confident man. I am confident
So I look like an idiot. Test C Shubham
Nobody has this doubt here. ok i will
Try to explain it to you one last time. If
If you understand then it is fine. Otherwise V
We will discuss it in our office separately.
That's not a waste of everyone's time here. V
Have [sound of clearing throat] a time
Crunch. I said ok sir try one more
Time. [Laughter]
Look, you can find any
Involve in sexual activity
You can't be. Whether consent or
No consent, whether you are a couple or married
be in any given scenario in any case what
So ever you can not indulge in any kind of
Sexual activity in this office premises.
You can do any activity in this office premises
Be involved in sexual activity
You can't.
I said one second, one second, one second.
Are you guys not open minded?
Thank you.
[Cheers]
[Appreciation]
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
[music]